

FULL STACK ENGINEER

Pontianak, Kalimantan Barat, Pontianak, 78113, Indonesia

081345663935

nidzammuzakki@gmail.com

#### SKILLS

Git Version Control

**RESTful API Integration** 

React.js knowledge

Node.js Experience

SQL Database Management

**Docker Containerization** 

Software Engineering

Python Programming (Al)

Progressive Web Apps

Microservices Architecture JIRA

Redis(PKWT, PKWTT) based on role and type employee (include init new service with unit test)

PostgreSQL

Cyber Security

Micro Frontend

KrakenD

Kafka

Redis

Golang

PERSONAL

## DETAILS

• Date of birth 30 May 1998

• Marital status Married

### ABOUT ME

•

I am a 25 year old single man, i was born in Pontianak on may 30th 1998. Has 1 years 5 months experience in IT Field as Golang Developer (microservice) & ReactJS Developer (microfrontend). Experienced in handling IT Project in financial services industry. Familiar to gather user Develop and manage the work breakdown structure (WBS) of information technology projects, creating project reports, project documentation. A fast learner who adapt quickly to change, eager to learn new things in Information and Technology, and discipline

**WORK EXPERIENCE** 

#### BACKEND DEVELOPER | NOV 2024 - PRESENT CIMB NIAGA, TANGERANG

### **API Portal Revamp**

- · create ecosystem BE (golang) from scratch
- create private repo for all library
- tech stack (microservice, redis, kafka, golang, postgresql, reactjs, sonarqube)

#### **Approval Engine** · design database

- · create documentation endpoint (insert, update approval include approve

· create endpoint get list approval engine with pagination, filter and search

- · create endpoint insert approval with rest api (communication)
- · create endpoint update approval include reject and approve, and push to
- kafka approval engine, push kafka to audit trail (message broker)

### **Audit Trail**

- · design database and create microservice audit-trail
- create documentation endpoint getList and consumer kafka · create endpoint list audit trail for activity log (user and data)
- · create consumer audit trail and save data to database

#### **Content Management Service** · design database and create microservice cms

- · create documentation endpoint crud cms and consumer kafka
- create endpoint crud cms (html, landing\_page, mock\_api, api\_list)
- create consumer from approval engine (kafka)
- · create produce kafka audit trail every endpoint crud
- **Auth Service**

#### · design database and create microservice auth

- · create documentation endpoint crud cms and consumer kafka
- · create endpoint register with send email and produce kafka audit trail
- create endpoint login, set token to redis and produce kafka audit trail
- · create endpoint logout, delete token from redis and produce kafka audit trail
- · create invitation by admin, send email and produce kafka audit trail
- · create endpoint detail user
- · create endpoint refresh token, set token to redis
- · create endpoint forgot password, send email, produce kafka audit trail
- $\cdot$  create endpoint change password from forgot password and produce kafka
- audit trail create endpoint change password from profile and produce kafka audit trail
- **Onboarding (Form Register API)**

#### · design database and create microservice onboarding form

- create documentation all endpoint form
- create endpoint download PDF, if form approved · create endpoint create form with (submit and validation) or draft
- · create endpoint approval when form submitted create endpoint upload file (jpg, pem (key), etc)

#### MOLADIN, REMOTE **Payment**

• FULL STACK ENGINEER | MAY 2023 - AUG 2024

#### · Manage and create payment in between moladin and midtrans (include BCA, Mandiri, BNI)

Insurance

**Employee Management** 

consistent with other service

- Manage and create disbursement between moladin and midtrans (include BCA, Mandiri, BNI)
- · Fixing or change Account number with status Dormant Manage account type or source account for disbursement moladin Create and manage Cancel payment
- · Create and manage Virtual Payment withaccount (BCA, Mandiri) · Tech stack: golang (BE), database MySQL, Redis, microservice, Kafka
- Implement logic calculation of life insurance with tenor (max 5 years) · Design Database Life Insurance
- · Create History of Calculation of Life Insurance Create Config Life Insurance (max principal and max age) per partner

and type employee (include init new service with unit test)

· Create logic Onboarding Employee include KK number and OCR KTP • Enhancement Logic Onboarding include data validate (blacklist) and

Tech Stack: Golang (BE), database MySQL, Redis, microservice (API CALL)

· Create logic and config Term and Condition based on Role (include init new service with unit test) Enchancment Final Review process employee

Create logic and config Aggrement Employee (PKWT, PKWTT) based on role

 Manage Kafka (Aggrement Employee) · Manage Config (dynamic TnC) Term and Condition for Employee

· Tech Stack: Golang BE, TypeScript BE, ReactJS, microservice, microfrontend,

Create Config for type and reason Block and Unblock Employee and Dealer

- Database MySQL, Redis, Kafka **Blacklist Engine**
- · Slicing Design from figma (Micro Front End VueJS) Create flow block and unblock user

· Create Unit Test (all modules include registration and transaction) with test

· Internal Pentester (the process of exploiting own system from an insider's

PT SOLUIX, TANGERANG **BCA Syariah** 

BACKEND DEVELOPER | DEC 2022 - MAR 2023

#### view to detect vulnerabilities before delivery to real pentester or external pentester) · Create and handle API Gateway (KrakenD)

container

- · Create Script for Load Testing and improve code quality BSI
  - Antasena

( FRONT END ENGINER | JAN 2021 - OCT 2022

• Build Frontend with ReactJs(Redux and Styled-Component) from scratch (Slicing Design from Figma)

Create Script for Load Testing (JMeter)

PT ADAPRO NUDA DATA, JAKARTA

· Create documentation about the frontend application · Maintenance and Enhancement

General Ledger/Core banking

- (Design)
- Build Restful Webservice from scratch with GoLang (Echo Framework) · Creating, integrating and managing database (SQL Server)

## **EDUCATION**

LINK

### STMIK PONTIANAK, PONTIANAK

● TEKNIK INFOMATIKA | 2020

· Maintenance and Enhancement

Teknik Infomatika

Bold Profile: https://www.linkedin.com/in/nidza

muddin-muzakki-560034202/

# (Design)

• Build Frontend with ReactJs(Redux and Styled-Component) from scratch (Slicing Design from Figma)

· Discuss with User and Designer about application requirements and Figma

Discuss with User and Designer about application requirements and Figma

- · Create documentation about the frontend and backend (postman) application